erste Faces
Pachi pachi no limit
the people of the time will come back.
We will continue to change the
world and the world with us.
Asus is it?
Don't let them fire those lasers attack
Damn!
Those boxes are closing in from all sides!
What do we do? Just shoot!
We'll get them before they can get us!
It's over.
Stand back!
I got this one!
Steam Knuckles!
You want to destroy those ships?
You're going to have to go through me!
All the vice-admirals have landed!
So where's the lab where they're
holding the Cipher pull agents?
Way up top.
The Navy and the robot
Seameast are fighting!
Oh, man, looks like they're going all out!
They should be safe for now.
Sentomaru is still in
command of our pacifistas.
Our defenses remain iron-tight.
And they know that!
Which is the whole reason
they sent him after Sentomaru!
Kizaru?
He's on the shore already?
Oh, no!
Closer.
He's fighting right below us.
Kizaru's here.
This brings back some unpleasant
memories from our first trip to Sabaori.
Well, you're screwed.
Sucks to be you.
Why does he have to fight
Kizaru about people?
I'm sorry, Sentomaru.
I won't blame you if you
choose to none of any.
What a crotch is to say.
It's gonna be okay, Scylla.
We don't have time to worry right now.
Just focus on cracking the cool.
Edison's right, we've got a job!
Let's do it!
Michelle!
I really would have had
to hurt you, friend.
Why don't you surrender for me?
Yasakani's Secret Jewel.
I'm not happy about this
myself, but I made a promise!
A deal with Straw Hat Luffy!
With Straw Hat?
Since when are you the kind of
man who makes deals with pirates?
I'll take any ally I can get!
I owe it to Pump to get him out of here!
I won't let him die!
Oh.
Well, ain't that a surprise.
Looks like our gang of bears
has already been taken care of.
Did that child beat them on his own?
I lived in the village,
but I won't go back there.
The people are all weak and stupid.
I see.
So they kicked you out, huh?
I'm strong enough to wrestle bears.
I don't get tired or
hungry, but I need a job.
And I need money.
Oh, is there something
important you need to buy?
Yes, rice balls.
Huh?
You were so adorable back then.
So, you need a job.
You've proven your strength.
I could put that to good use.
Well, boy, what would you
say to becoming my bodyguard?
You really want to hire
me? Yes! I'll do it!
Uncle!
Huh? What?
Are you talking to me?
Help me, Uncle.
I've never been a bodyguard.
How should I keep on safe?
Kid, I am not your uncle.
Well, at least you're
not calling me gramps.
Teach me everything you know.
I'll train hard!
I tried my best to teach you, Sentomaru.
I really did.
Sumo strike!
But you forget.
For as much as you brag
about your defense...
Mine is just as good.
Come in, Pasapistas.
Your previous commander is currently
unconscious, but your mission has changed.
You will provide support to the
Navy fleet surrounding Egghead.
Sink the Sea Beast weapon.
We command the pacifistas now.
That order was revised.
Quite the waste to sink those sea beasts,
but far better to save the pacifistas.
Seems there's been sizable damage.
Give me a report. Yes, sir.
Kizaru just took out Sentomaru! He wants!
We need to shut down this
defense system immediately!
Roger!
It can't let Sentomaru's
iPhone go to race!
He bought us his car!
You'll never crack it!
Trust me, I'm Dr.
Vegapunk, heard of me?
Chizuru is lighted, sir.
He can get Pospa Lizabella in an instant.
What?
You really got no
defenses against this guy?
Precisely.
What the hell are we supposed to do now?
He kicked our butts when
we fought him before.
Looks like we get around soon.
Let's see how long your strides last.
We're giving some hustle, yeah?
As soon as that barrier comes
down, this ship's gotta fly!
You're doing great, don't you worry.
I'll have everything
in position in no time.
We're counting on you.
We'd better eat while we still can, Luffy.
Good point.
You can't bite on an empty stomach, I say.
Hey, did you two try to focus?
Don't stuff your faces when
we're about to blast off.
Hey, Lily!
What's that alarm?
It sounds like somebody broke
in, but I don't know how.
Who could get through the barrier?
It's supposed to be impenetrable!
They gave me a checklist of
things I shouldn't destroy.
First off was the power plant
followed by punk records and york
it's a real pity that my dear old
friend didn't make the list this time
the list of what i have to destroy
is shorter just one man dr vega punk
The barrier was useless,
Gizaru's inside the dome!
Wait, wait, wait!
Where are Lupi and the others?
They're stuck out there with him.
What do I know?
No!
Tell them through the snail!
They have no idea!
Lupi!
Run for your life!
Our plan won't succeed unless
the ship is in position.
The barrier stays up to zen.
DUDE CY!
Filthy bastard!
Let me borrow this.
What the hell?
Why am I the one in a damn bubble?
It's your partner's fault, not mine.
You think you own this place
because your buddy's here?
You can't defeat me and Kizaru.
The noose is tightening around your neck
you don't know what we're capable of
I wondered why I didn't see
their ship on the shoreline.
Look at you, sneaking away.
We've got to hurry!
Kizaru, a freaking admiral?
What's our plan, Luffy?
Please don't tell me he ran off.
Hey, Luffy!
Straw Hat.
Long time, Wilma.
I see your manners haven't improved.
I'll warn you.
We're not the same as two years ago.
We're a hundred times stronger.
The invincible slave has returned!
We don't know what he wants!
Be careful!
Stop him, you fools!
That monster is destroying our city!
Why is he doing this?
He's too strong.
We can't hold him back.
URSA SHARK!
HOW DARE YOU!
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A SLAVE!
What the hell are you trying to pull?
The revolutionaries gave
us enough mess to clean up.
If you got an explanation,
I'd love to hear it, Kuma.
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki.
You're useless.
We can't rely on you soldiers for a thing.
Hey!
Speaking of which!
I wanted lobster for dinner.
But there was not to be found.
It's an unprecedented disaster.
What's happening to the
holy land's food supply?
Have them hide your dinner plans.
I've been injured.
For this rock-paging Hope.
A disobedient slave must be dealt with.
Stop fooling around and kill him.
Already.
You know the deal.
We can't let you run around free.
Kuma you're too dangerous.
Either we Keep you on a leash
or we put you in the ground.
You should have lost
all sense of identity.
That makes you as good as dead. Already.
So what are you trying to accomplish here?
I didn't know you could
still bleed like a human.
You get back here!
No way away!
Oh my god!
Woof!
Arrrgh!
You can bark all you like,
but Kuma's mind is long gone.
He'll be reborn as a weapon.
He even volunteered for the process.
You're a liar!
He'd never do that.
Not unless you forced him to!
He wouldn't leave me!
He wouldn't throw his whole life away!
Hey!
Did you let Kuma escape?
Why aren't you doing your job?
You're the fleet admiral, aren't you?
You're just a puppet.
Think for yourself.
Or act for yourself.
So where the hell could
you be going on your own?
Pacifistas and all marines!
Continue your assault!
Destroy every last sea beast weapon!
Occupy the Fabrio phase.
We're seizing the whole island.
Admiral Kizaru is above the clouds.
He's just entered the Lobby phase.
I see how you managed to beat Kaido.
You're certainly tough
enough, but I wonder.
What business does a pirate
like you have protecting Dr.
Vegapunk?
You're putting a lot on the line for him.
What business do you
have trying to kill him?
Old Man Apple helped you guys a lot.
Why do you want to get rid of him?
It's not that I want to.
How far up is he going?
I'd rather not kill him at all.
I've known Vegapunk for a long time.
So to be frank, I don't
need to hear your opinion.
Acceleration is power.
It's complete!
Its name is Vega Force One!
So dream of all mankind!
It's a giant robot!
Help me!
No, don't just hit me!
Thank God evil never dies
Bungie! What?
Uh, Lillard.
We gotta run!
Come on, let's go!
Let's get it close!
Whoa!
How dare you!
The Vagabur's one was the dream
event kind you've been jerking!
That's it, bro.
You are gonna pay!
Is the sonny all right?
Hold up!
Might want to check on Straw
Hat while you're at it!
Kizaru, you bastard!
Why, I hardly recognized you, Bonnie.
My word.
Kids these days grow up real fast.
So what's your stick in this?
Did you want to take revenge
on Vegapunk yourself?
Are you mad we're gonna
beat you to the punch?
Shut up.
Vegapunk isn't the one I'm
trying to kill anymore.
AIME Satori!
You're not part of my mission.
So don't make me shoot down
another acquaintance, please.
No! The Barrier!
Bonnie!
Enough, Kizaru!
You're done for!
Radical...
BASSION!
Wait.
He's gone?
Kizaru!
Where'd he go?
Stella's in danger.
Franky, call the control room!
Yo, control room!
Hey, Franky, you okay?
I just heard a big explosion over there!
Never mind me!
Are you guys safe?
Yeah? Why?
Oh, I guess he's not
there yet. Lucky break.
You are making me nervous.
It is done!
That puny encryption was no match for us.
We're free!
Nice work!
Eat that, York! You lose!
We're so stupid pumpkin geniuses!
Hello, Franky.
We can deactivate the
barrier any time you like.
Did you move the Vega Force One
and the ship to the back side yet?
Nah, it's complicated.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news,
But your escape plan is a bust.
Hello, old friend.
Isaru! I don't know.
When did you get here?
Wait, so what did you do to Luffy?
You didn't kill him, did you?
He's so dead.
Are you the cause of
that explosion earlier?
Uh-huh.
It was a bit of a tragedy.
That robot you loved
so much, I blew it up.
What?
How could you?
I want you to understand something.
This mission is very difficult for me.
I'd rather not draw this out.
What was that?
What fresh hell is this?
We've suffered enough!
Phew!
That was spicy!
You're back, huh?
So this must be...
Guess who survived the
zappy barrier twice!
Man, you threw me into that thing fast!
Anyone smell burnt rubber?
Thank you.
It's time to go to the end of the day.